hallmarkchannel.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy | Hallmark Channel

**CROWN MEDIA FAMILY NETWORKS**

 **PRIVACY POLICY**

 **PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE.**

 **GENERAL**  
Crown Media United States, LLC and/or its parent companies, subsidiaries, agents or affiliated companies (collectively, “Crown Media,” "we" or "us") owns, operates and/or provides this and other websites, applications, pages on social networks (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, Instagram) and other online or wireless services (each, a "Website" and collectively, the “Websites”). By accessing and/or using the Websites, you agree that both your access to and use of the Websites are governed by this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use located at www.hallmarkchannel.com/crown-media-family-networks-terms-of-use (collectively, the “Privacy Policy”), as well as all applicable laws, rules and regulations and rules governing promotions. 

**TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**   
For various purposes to provide and improve our service to you, we collect several different types of information.

 ** _Personal Data._** While using the Websites, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”), which may include, but is not limited to:· 

· First and last name  
· User name and password  
· Email address  
· Phone number  
· Address, City, State, ZIP/Postal code   
· Cable/Satellite/Wireless/Mobile Service Provider  
· Birthdate  
· Gender

 ** _Usage Data._ **We may also collect information how the Websites are accessed and used by you (“Usage Data”). Usage Data may include, without limitation, information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Websites that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

 **USE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
We may use the information we collect from you to:

· Provide and maintain the Websites  
· Notify you about changes to the Websites  
· Gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Websites  
· Monitor the usage of our Websites  
· Detect, prevent and address technical issues  
· Provide you with news, special offers and general information about other services which we offer that are similar to those that you have already acquired, unless you have opted not to receive such information  
· Assess your job application and communicate with you about this if you have applied for a job vacancy posted on the Websites  
· Share with third-party promotional partners if you have given us permission to do so   
· Comply with applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and our policies

You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us. Please note that participation in some activities offered on our Websites may be limited without the submission of certain Personal Data.

 **THIRD PARTY TRACKING AND ONLINE ADVERTISING**  
We may share, or we may permit third party online advertising networks, social media companies and other third party services, to collect, information about your use of our Websites so that they may play or display ads on our Websites, on other devices you may use, and on other websites, apps or services. We and our third party partners use this information to make advertisements you see online more relevant to your interests. Depending on your browser or mobile device, you may be able set your browser to delete or notify you of cookies and other tracking technology by actively managing the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please note that blocking or deleting cookies may negatively impact your experience using the Websites, as some features and services on our Websites may not work properly. Our third party online advertisers are not subject to this Privacy Policy. Please read the applicable privacy policy to determine how they will use any information they collect from you.

You may be able to limit interest-based advertising through the settings on your mobile device by selecting “limit ad tracking” (iOS) or “opt-out of interest based ads” (Android). To learn more about interest-based advertising and how you may be able to opt-out of some of this advertising, you may wish to visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at www.networkadvertising.org/choices, and/or the DAA’s resources atwww.aboutads.info/choices. Some of these opt-outs may not be effective unless your browser is set to accept cookies. 

**COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES TO COLLECT INFORMATION**  
Like most websites and online services, we automatically collect certain types of usage information when you visit our Websites, read our emails, or otherwise engage with us. We typically collect this information through a variety of tracking technologies, including cookies, web beacons, embedded scripts, location-identifying technologies, and similar technology. These tracking technologies collect information such as how you use the Websites, information about your browser and online usage patterns, information about the devices you use to access the Websites and your geographical location data. We may link your various devices so that content you see on one device can result in relevant advertising and content displayed on another device, and so that we may recognize and contact you on the various devices you may use. We may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Websites. 

If you would prefer not to accept cookies, most browsers will allow you to change your browser settings to notify you when you receive a cookie, which lets you choose whether or not to accept it, disable existing cookies or set your browser to automatically reject cookies. Please note that blocking or disabling cookies may negatively impact your experience using the Websites, as some features and services on our Websites may not work properly. Depending on your mobile device and operating system, you may not be able to delete or block all cookies. You may also set your email options to prevent the automatic downloading of images that may contain technologies that would allow us to know whether you have accessed our email and performed certain functions with it. ** __**

**SECURITY**  
We will employ reasonable precautions to protect personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Such measures may include the use of password protection and restricting access to personal information to those with a legitimate purpose in receiving the information. We take reasonable steps to accommodate privacy preferences and help ensure that the personal information is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete and current. 

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches of our Websites and records no website or Internet transmission is completely secure and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur.

 **CHILDREN AND PRIVACY**  
When subscribing to our email newsletters or when entering information on our Websites in connection with an online sweepstakes, contest, survey, registration, product or service, we ask for users to state their age and/or birth date. We rely on our users to be truthful in responding to these questions. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. We encourage users under the age of 18 not to submit personal information to us. The age of eligibility may be greater than 18 years of age when entering an online contest or sweepstakes as stated in the official rules of each such contest or sweepstakes. 

**COMMUNITY AND PUBLIC AREAS**   
Information posted to message boards and chat areas is available to the general public. Please use caution when posting any such information. Users under the age of 18 should be particularly careful not to provide any personally identifying information while using chat rooms or message boards. Users of chat areas and message boards must follow acceptable standards of behavior when posting messages online. We reserve the right to, but is not obligated to, refuse or delete any content that in our sole discretion is considered inappropriate. 

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**   
Our Websites contain links to third party sites other than our own. Those sites may not follow the same privacy policy as us. Such links may be to advertisers, content providers or partners who may use our logo and/or style as a result of a co-branding agreement. These sites may send their own cookies to you and may collect information and use it in a way inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. We do not control the content that appears on these third party sites. The use of any information or materials that you may access at these third party sites is purely voluntary. You should not rely on their content without independent and thorough review of the accuracy, completeness, effectiveness, timeliness and correct sequencing. When you click a link to such third party sites from our Websites you should read the applicable privacy policy to determine how they will use any information they collect from you. These third party sites may also refer to specific commercial products, processes, or services by trade name, trademark, service mark, manufacturer or otherwise. Unless we have provided explicit authority, such references in no way indicate our endorsement, recommendation or preference. 

**GENERAL**  
This Privacy Policy shall operate to the fullest extent permitted by law. If any provision or part of this Privacy Policy is held unlawful, void or unenforceable it shall not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions of this Privacy Policy.

 **CONTACT US**  
From time to time we may revise this Privacy Policy. Therefore, to keep up to date with our current policy you should review it periodically. If you have any questions or wish to communicate with us, please contact us at:   
(888) 390-7474 

**Updated: September 19, 2018**
